前情提要
Previously on The Strain...
爸爸 发生了什么事
Dad, what's happening?
这是我们正在调查的传染病的一部分
This is part of the epidemic we've been investigating.
马特被感染了
Matt was infected.
现在我要你告诉我
Now I need you to tell me:
你上次和你妈妈联系是什么时候
when was the last time you heard from your mother?
今天上午
This morning.
他们正在为你争吵 因为你要我们去佛蒙特州
They were arguing about you because you told us to go to Vermont.
马特昨晚甚至没有回家
Matt didn't even come home last night.
你知道艾尔德里奇 帕尔默是谁吗
Do you know who Eldritch Palmer is?
世界上最有权势的人之一 是的
One of the most powerful men in the world, yes.
他雇佣了我
He hired me.
你干了什么
What did you do?
我尽我最大的能力瘫痪了因特网
I worked my ass off to shut the internet down.
我们可以找到血祖
We can get the Master.
他闭不出户 就在这个城市的某个地方
He's nesting. Somewhere in the city.
但是我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
凯莉在哪儿
Where's Kelly?
凯莉失联一整天了
Kelly's MIA all day.
扎克在哪 伊弗
Where's Zack, Eph?
他和我的同事们在一起
He's with my colleagues.
这里不安全
It's not safe here.
对啊 对啊 在你觉得事态如此严重的时候
Right, right. In all your concerned state,
还能抽时间滚床单
you still find time to screw on the rug.
她说真的 你必须尽快地离开这个镇子
She's serious. You have to get out of town as soon as possible.
嘿 你伤害了我的朋友 我会挖出你的心的
Hey. You hurt my friend, I will cut your heart out.
我爱我的妻子 他是我儿子的母亲
I love my wife. She's the mother of my son.
我会不惜一切来找到她的
I'd do anything to find her.
哈莱姆区 东118街
是的
Yes!
啊 该死
Aw, crap.
不 拜托 拜托了 给力点啊
No, come on! Please! Work!
好了
Yes!
爸爸 爸爸 来这儿
Dad! Dad, come here!
- 怎么了 出了什么事 - 妈妈的手机 它动了
- What is it? What's wrong? - Mom's phone, it moved.
- 她在移动 - 你在说什么呢
- She's moving. - What are you talking about?
几个月前我丢失了我的手机
I lost my phone a couple months ago.
我用这个网站来追踪它
I used this website to track it.
所以我想 你明白的 或许我们可以用这个来追踪她
So I thought, you know, maybe we could use it on her.
你能上网了
You got online?
几乎上不了 它超级慢 但是我最终找到了信号
Barely. It's super slow, but I finally got enough of a signal.
信号时有时无 但是也足够我监测到手机的移动了
It's going in and out but I got enough to see the phone move.
- 你确定它正在移动吗 - 是的 大概是3个街区
- You're sure it's moving? - Yeah. Like 3 blocks.
如果她正在移动 那她就应该还好 对吗
If she's moving, she's gotta be ok, right?
- 这是个好的现象 - 我要给她打电话
- It's a good sign. - I'm going to call her.
爸爸 手机响了
Dad, it's ringing.
嗨 我是凯莉 请留言
Hi, it's Kelly. Leave me a message
我尽快回复你的 谢谢
and I'll call you right back. Thanks.
妈妈 又是我 给我回电话 好吗 拜托了
Mom, it's me again. Call me back, ok? Please?
或许她的手机是静音或者别的什么状态
Maybe it's on silent or something.
为什么她还不打回来
Why hasn't she called back?
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
- 她在哪片区域 - 这里显示是在
- What was the location? - This says...
翻译：Espionage Jophy 烈焰鸟     校对：Jophy
在主街和前街的交叉口
Main and Front.
- 不 拜托了 拜托 快动啊 - 嘘 没事的 没事的
- No! Come on, please! Work! - Shh. It's ok. It's ok.
我们已经知道她的位置了
We know her location.
后期：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎     总监：Jophy
我会找到她的
I'll get her.
合作贴吧：百度《美剧血族》吧
百度《美剧血族》吧
血族
第一季  第十集
总统已经宣布了所有银行停业
The President has declared a bank holiday in an attempt
旨在稳定国家震荡的金融系统
to stabilize the nation's teetering financial system.
最新的政策随着
This latest move comes
昨日23家银行于昨日倒闭而发布了
in the wake of 23 bank failures yesterday.
尽管已经有这些措施
Despite these measures,
国际货币基金组织首脑
the head of the International Monetary Fund
在今天的新闻发布会上透露
hinted in a news conference today
世界金融系统依旧在震荡
that the world financial system is now teetering
- 正濒临系统 - 发生了什么事
- on the brink of systematic-- - What's going on?
扎克追踪到了凯莉的手机了
Zack tracked down Kelly's phone.
这就是你爱的那个男人吗
妈妈先把你的茶喝掉吧 别凉了
早上好 马丁内兹夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Martinez.
手机正在移动
The phone is moving.
- 在哪儿 - 阿斯托利亚
- Where is it? - Astoria.
- 别说了 - 我没打算说了
- Don't say it. - I wasn't gonna.
凯莉可能还活着
Kelly could be alive.
手机在白天移动
The phone is moving during daylight.
她可能已经出来了而没有被困住 我们做到了
She could've gotten out without getting stung. We did.
他们正在动员楼下
They're mobilizing downstairs.
塞特拉基安有个计划
Setrakian has a plan.
我必须要先干这件事了
I have to do this first.
昨晚我并不是想要伤害你
I didn't mean to hurt you last night.
都是些没意义的事情
Nothing makes any sense anymore.
我当时不知道我在说些什么
I don't know what I'm saying,
我在做些什么 但是我后来知道了
what I'm doing, but I knew what I was doing then.
我并不为此感到后悔
I'm not sorry about that.
我知道你想要为我做最坏的打算
I know you tried to prepare me for the worst
但是我认为现在有一个真正的机会
but I think there's a real chance here
- 而只要有 - 你就会去尝试
- and so long as there is-- - Then you should go.
但是你必须为你可能找到的东西做好准备
But you must be prepared for what you might find.
我明白
I get it.
带上你的武器
Take your weapons.
- 有什么变化吗 - 还是在相同的地方
- Any change? - Still in the same place.
我不能一起去吗 我不想就只是坐在这儿
Can't I come? I don't want to just sit here.
不 我需要你追踪手机
No, I need you to track the phone.
如果信号移动了就发短信给我
Text me if the signal moves.
如果短信联系不上呢
What if it doesn't go through?
那就一直发
Keep texting.
把妈妈带回来
Bring mom back with you.
我追踪到没有老鼠的区域的中心
I tracked the epicenter of the rat-free zone.
正好就在世贸中心
Right down here by the World Trade Center.
我钻到这些管道里面去调查
I popped down into the tunnels to investigate,
最终和几打吸血鬼面对面了 真是愉快的一天
ended up eye-to-eye with a few dozen of them. It was a fun day.
依我看来 在他们的地盘上发动攻击
In my opinion, attacking them head-on on their own turf
似乎是大家一起找死的好方法
seems like a good way for us all to die.
重点是老鼠总是有后门可以逃脱
The thing about rats is they always have a backdoor -
所以抓住它们相当难
that's why it's so tricky to catch them.
我打赌那些吸血鬼 我跟你打赌他们也有一个后门
I bet that the vamps... I bet you they have one, too.
这也是我所想的 好吗
So this is my thinking, alright?
我们必须监测世贸中心附近
We have to look at all the decommissioned tunnels and lines
所有废弃的管道和线路 而这张地图
near the World Trade Center, which this map...
帮不了我们多少
doesn't help us very much.
如果能连上网就好了
It'd be great to get online.
我知道网上有个很厉害的交通档案库
I know this great transit archive on there.
网络瘫掉了 所以
The Internet's for shit, so...
- 好啦 对此很抱歉 - 对什么
- Yeah, sorry about for that. - About what?
是我瘫痪了网络
I brought it down.
嗯 我错过了这部分情况
Uh... I think I missed that.
嗯 不仅仅是我 我和我的团队
Yeah, not just me... but my crew.
一个富有的老家伙聘请了我们去截断移动服务
An old rich guy hired us to interrupt mobile services
并搞垮了大部分的网络通道
and crash most Internet traffic.
艾尔德里奇 帕尔默
Eldritch Palmer.
阻止信息的传播
Preventing the spread of information.
- 而你们帮助了他 - 我从来没想伤害人
- And you helped him?! - I never wanted to hurt people.
我已经努力寻找补救的方法了
I have been trying to figure out a way to make things right.
- 你能做到吗 - 也许可以
- Can you do that? - Maybe.
如果我能回到帕尔默的办公室就行
If I can get back into Palmer's offices.
- 你要怎么进去呢 - 我能让她进去
- How would you get access? - I could get her in.
用我公务员的身份 躲过监测进去
Use my city credentials. Fly under the radar.
- 没问题 我当你的老板 - 助手
- Sure, I could be your boss. - Assistant.
- 老板 -小事
- Boss. - Details.
我总是想进入那幢建筑
I always wanted to get into that building.
快 我们走
Keep up, let's go!
嘿 宝贝 这个世界就要完蛋了 你想
Hey baby, the world about to end. You want,
嘿 你从哪儿搞到那个手机的
Hey, where'd you get that phone?
- 那是我的 那是我的手机 - 我知道是你偷的
- That's mine. That's my phone. - I know you stole it.
被你偷手机的那个女人在哪儿
Where's the woman you took it from?
你在哪儿找到这个手机的
Where'd you find it?!
离我远点不然我屁都不会告诉你的
Back off or I'm not telling you shit.
我在街上捡到它的 旁边可没有什么女人
I found this on the street. Wasn't any woman with it.
你带我看看在哪儿
You're gonna show me where.
给我看看你的证件 条子
Show me your badge po-po.
我看起来像个警察吗 我是个医生
Do I look like a cop? I'm a doctor.
真的吗
For real?
我的腿感染了
It's infected.
天啊 这烧伤可真严重
Jesus christ that's a bad burn.
- 你感染多久了 - 上周感染的
- How long have you had that? - Got it last week.
好的 布瑞亚 你在哪儿找到这个手机的
Ok, Brea. Where did you find the phone?
拉我起来
Help me up.
谢谢我
Thank you.
在那儿 就在那儿
There. It was right there.
- 你看见开车的那女人了吗 - 没有
- Did you see the woman driving? - No.
32小时之前
皇后区伍德赛德 凯尔顿街道
马特
Matt?
Matt?!
你知道的 不沟通也是毁了我的婚姻的一部分原因
You know not talking is part of what ended my marriage.
天啊 你成熟点吧
God! Way to be a grownup!
听着 如果你不想谈 至少要让我进去
Look, if you don't want to talk, at least let me in.
我需要准备上班了
I need to get ready for work.
布鲁克林  布鲁克林高地426号公立学校
-她真刻薄 -嘿 你有来啊
- She's so mean. - Hey, you're here.
今天要上课 不是吗
It's a school day, right?
是的 但大概一半的孩子都缺勤
Yeah, but like half the kids are out.
大部分教职工也是
Most of the staff, too.
-他们病了吗 -我想是吧
- Are they sick? - I guess.
他们大部分人甚至连打电话请假都没有
A bunch of them didn't even bother to call in.
米兰达打算让孩子们早点下课
Miranda is going to release the kids early.
出勤人数还不到一半 还教什么啊
No point with barely half attendance.
怎么了
What?
你是不是知道些什么
Do you know something?
伊弗警告过我有一种病毒
Eph warned me about a virus.
跟肯尼迪机场有什么关联的
Something to do with that plane at JFK.
说我们该离开城镇
Said we should leave town.
真的吗
Seriously?
哦 天啊
Oh God.
如果你想跟米兰达说 就去吧
If you want to let Miranda know.
但我要去接扎克出城
But I'm getting Zack and I'm getting out of town.
你也该离开城镇
You should, too.
马特
Matt?
你在哪里
Where are you?
学校放半天假 大家都病了
Called a half day at school. Everyone is sick.
伊弗是对的
Eph was right.
马特
Matt?
别闹了
Enough already!
你听到我的话了吗 伊弗是对的
Did you hear me? Eph was right.
而你却叫FBI抓走他
And you had him arrested by the FBI--
哦 天啊 马特
Oh my God, Matt?
扎克
Zack?
布鲁克林  弗朗西斯学院
亲爱的 你在哪里
Sweetheart, where are you?
有一些人似乎
An equal number of people who intend,
想要亲自结束这场危机
it seems to be, to take matters into their own hands.
枪支的销量直线上升
Firearm sales have spiked...
生存设备 煤气罐 发电机
Survival equipment, propane tanks, generators,
罐头食品等等也一样
canned food and the likes--
凯莉
Kelly?
我的天啊 你还好吗
Oh my world. Are you ok?
扎克在哪里 我来接他的
Where's zack? I'm here to pick him up.
我来迟了吗
Am I late?
我 我想是来迟了
I-- I think I'm late.
我们很早就放学了 又联系不上你
We dismissed early and when we couldn't reach you,
你的朋友戴安娜来接走了他 我是说
your friend Diane came to pick him up, I mean...
我知道你们拼车 凯莉
I know that you carpool. Look, Kelly,
我想你是不是出了事故
I think maybe you've been in an accident
我们应该送你去医院
and we should Get you to a hospital.
你能帮我联系上扎克吗
Can you get Zack for me?
-求你了 -呃 我
- Please? - Mm-hmm. I uh...
不好意思
If you'll just excuse me,
我先去打个电话 好吗
I'm just going to make one call, ok?
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我猜她可能出车祸了
I'm guessing that she's been in a car accident
我觉得她有点脑震荡
and I think that she has a concussion.
喂
Hello?
凯莉
Kelly...
滚开
Back off!
好了 小助手 只要你坚信你应该去那里
Ok, assistant. You believe you're supposed to be there,
-那他们就会相信你的 -当然
- they'll believe it. - Sure.
这不是我第一次干这种事 有脑有力先生
You know this isn't my first dance, o' wise and powerful.
当铺的那个老头是什么来头
So what's with the old pawn shop guy?
你怎么跟他成为朋友的
How are you friends with him?
我昨晚才认识他的 就跟你一样
Met him last night. Same as you.
真的吗
Really? Huh.
倒是进展的蛮快的啊
Seemed to have such a shorthand.
你呢 你又是什么来历
What about you? What's your story?
没什么来历 就如你所见
No story. What you see is what you get.
听着 亲爱的 当铺那家伙是个吸血鬼猎人
Listen, honey. The pawn shop guy is a vampire killer.
如果你神秘的背景比他的更来来头的话
If you could top that story with your mysterious background,
那就 说出来吧
then... go for it.
好吧 你想知道什么
Fine. What do you want to know about me?
帕尔默这家伙
This guy Palmer.
找你去开启世界末日
Guy dicks you over to bring about end times?
如果我们只是去趟他的老窝蹭点无线网
If we're going to his building just to borrow his wifi
那你就是在浪费我的时间
then you're wasting my time.
我肯定不会浪费你的时间
I wouldn't dream of wasting your time.
石心集团 曼哈顿  57西街156号
你好
Hello.
纽约虫害控制中心
Uh, New York Pest Control Services.
我们要检查一下你们的行政餐饮设施
We have to inspect your executive dining facilities.
我没有找到你的预约
I don't have you down here.
我们检查都不让
Well they don't let us
事先预约的
make appointments for inspections, you know?
没有保全系统确认 我不能让你进去的
I can't let you through without an OK from security.
你确定吗
You're sure about that?
我们只是快速的看一下
It's pretty much just a quick look-see.
我们只是需要应付一下我麻烦的领导
You know, another box I have to check off for my hard-ass boss.
10分钟内就能完事
In and out in 10?
嗯 行政餐饮中心好像正在换班时间
Well, it looks like executive dining is in between shifts anyway.
-所以 哦 太好了
- So... - Oh, perfect.
中间的电梯 25楼
Middle elevator. 25th floor.
谢谢洛伦 你最好了
Thanks Lauren. You're the best.
祝你一整天都心情愉快 好吗
And you have yourself a great day, ok?
-好 -谢谢
- Ok. - Thanks.
自信 这一切都来源于自信
Confidence. It's all about confidence.
-请跟我们来 好吗 -自信还是自强
- Will you follow us, please? - Confidence or competence?
听着 我不想找你们的麻烦
Now look, I don't want to get you boys in trouble.
但作为纽约的害虫稽查员
But as Pest Inspectors for the city of New York,
我们有权进入任何一家执证经营的食品机构
we have the absolute right to enter any licenced food...
嘿 闭嘴
Hey. Shut up.
好的 谢谢你
Alright. Thank you.
维尔德斯女士
Ms. Velders.
我是雷吉 费斯威廉 你还记得我吗
Reggie Fitzwilliam, you remember me?
我对你可是印象深刻
'Cause I certainly remember you.
看来你改行抓老鼠了
I see you've taken up rat catching.
看起来是
So it appears.
搜他们身
Search them.
被碰我
Don't touch me.
-用这些抓老鼠 -用来对付大只的
- Use these for catching rats? - Only really big ones.
-现在要怎样 -帕尔默先生要见你
- So what now? - Mr. Palmer would like to see you.
不 不是你
No, not you.
她 单独一人
Her. Alone.
凯莉
Kelly?
你在吗
You here?
我们现在在另一场离奇凶案现场进行直播
We're live at the scene of of another bizarre murders.
今晚这起凶案的不幸遇害者
This tragic incident claimed the lives
是布鲁克林的一对年轻夫妇
of a young married couple here in Brooklyn tonight.
在邻居投诉
They were found in the basement of their home
有一股恶臭传出来之后
after a neighbor complained
他们在自家的地下室被发现
of a terrible smell emanating from inside.
警方表示 一场令人担忧的暴力活动
Police sources say a disturbing pattern of random violence
已经席卷纽约城了
has swept across New York City.
近期 警方接到了大量的
In recent days, police have been inundated with reports
入室袭击报警
of home invasions and attacks...
我的天啊 我的天啊 凯凯
Oh my God! Oh my God, Kel!
你吓死我了 几点了
You scared the crap out of me. What time is it?
凯凯
Kel?
凯莉
Kelly?
这是马特干的吗 你是说真的吗
Matt did this? Are you serious?
-扎克在哪里 -什么
- Where's Zack...? - What...
你是说问扎克在哪里吗
What do you mean where's zack?
伊弗说扎克跟他在一起
Eph said zack was with him.
凯凯 亲爱的 你知道吗 你快把我吓死了 好吗
Kel, honey, you know what? You're freaking me out, OK?
我带你去急诊室 好吗
So I'm going to take you to the emergency room, OK?
妈妈
Mom?
怎么了
What's... What's going on?
凯莉 你
Kelly! What the...
啊 你在干什么啊
Ah! What the hell are you doing?!
你在干什么 不
What are you doing?! No!
行了
Ok.
天啊 你还回来做什么
Why in God's name would you ever come back here?
因为我不喜欢被欺骗
Because I don't like being taken for a ride.
现在我知道帕尔默就是这一切的幕后黑手
Now I know that Palmer's behind all this.
而显然你愿意做他的走狗 但我不愿意
Evidently you're fine with being his lackey. I am not.
帕尔默先生病得很重
Mr. Palmer is very ill.
我不会让你伤害他的
I won't let you harm him.
要是你敢动他一分一毫
If you try anything, anything at all,
我会杀了你的
I'll kill you.
听明白了吗
Am I clear?
维尔德斯女士 应邀前来了
Ms. Valders. As requested.
维尔德斯女士
Ah. Ms. Valders.
我很佩服你的勇气
I so admire your pluck.
你以为你和 那个谁 一个抓老鼠的
Thinking you and...who? A rat catcher?
能来着 然后怎样
Could come here and...What?
除掉我吗
Dispense with me?
如此愚蠢可笑的计划真是令人震惊
The mind boggles at the absurdity of the plan.
但计划背后的你们 还挺大胆的
But the ego behind it... Audacious.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我们当时可是做了交易的
Did we have a deeper transaction than I recall?
-我花钱买了你 你帮我完成事情 -你也是个吸血鬼吗
- I bought you. You let me. - Are you a vampire, too?
完全不是
Hardly.
你想要毁灭世界 让人类灭绝
You wanted to bring the world down. Wipe out the human race.
一个有理智的人会干这种事吗
Why would any rational person want to do such a thing?
首先 不要否认你自己在这件事上的功劳
First, don't deny yourself due credit.
你可以鞠躬谢幕了 你做的很出色
You should be taking a bow. You did exceptional work.
说真的 没有你这件事我做不来
Truly. I couldn't have done this without you.
人类的DNA随着年龄的增长而衰退
Human DNA decays as we age.
随着时间的流逝 它会受损 会衰退
Over time, it frays and it fails
我们的生命也随之逝去
and we follow suit.
但是 遗传的密码可以被重写
But, it's a code that can be rewritten.
就像你重新编程软件然后就能掌控硬件
Rewrite the software and you control the hardware:
也就是人类的肌肉和组织
The meat, muscle, and tissue that is mankind.
目的是什么
To what end?
如果黑客入侵是为了探索可能性的极限
If hacking is about exploring the limits of what is possible,
那么 我的目的 用你的话来说
then I am on the verge of achieving what you would consider
就是终极入侵
the ultimate hack.
-欺骗死神 -长生不老
- Cheating death. - Immortality?
是的
Yes.
-非常感谢你的分享 -梦想即将实现
- Well thanks for sharing. - It's hard to be on the verge
的喜悦很难
of something so exciting
不跟别人分享
and not share the good news with someone.
-而你是最佳人选 -为什么
- And you are the perfect person. - And how's that?
因为 就是你说出去 谁又会相信呢
Well, who would listen to you if you shared it?
你不过是名无名小卒
You are insignificant.
你知道你自己有多么不起眼的
You feel how invisible you are.
所以你才为我做了那些事
That's why you did what you did for me.
-我说得对吗 -狗惹的
- Am I right about that? - Son of a bitch!
你 你浑蛋 放开我
You...you asshole! Let go of me!
你什么也不是 你
You're the nothing. You.
-我们不想再见到她了 -放开我
- We won't see her again. - Get off me.
不 先生 你不会再见到她了
No, sir. You will not.
放开我
Get off me!
15小时之前
凯莉
Kelly....
Kelly.
到我这儿来
Come to me.
到我这儿来 凯莉
Come to me, kelly.
凯莉
Kelly.
到我这儿来
Come to me.
看着我
Look at me!
尽情庆祝吧
Rejoice.
尽情拥抱你光荣的命运
Embrace your glorious fate.
嘿 魅力先生 记得要提醒我下次不要理你
Hey Mr. Charming, remind me to ignore you next time.
当然 下次会的 我们会用你的方式
Sure, next time I will. We'll do it your way.
叫喊的 杀出一条血路
We'll shout, yell, shoot our way in.
我本来有个更好的机会
Yeah, well I had a better chance.
停下来
Stop.
转过身来
Turn around.
放松
Relax.
我会让你们走的
I'm letting you go.
我的老板已经误入歧途了
My employer is... misguided.
那可不是一句 误入歧途 就能形容的
Misguided is not the bloody word I would use.
我不太认同他所做的
I don't agree with what he's doing,
我觉得我很难执行这种命令
so I can hardly carry out an order to kill the people
去杀那些试图纠正的人
who are trying to make it right.
你的朋友们不会告发你吗
Won't your friends here tell on you?
他们忠诚于我
Their loyalty is to me.
那你为什么不如加入我们
Then why don't you all join us?
帮助我们做正确的事情
Help us make this right.
去吧 趁你还有机会
Go. While you have a chance.
快走
Go.
戴安
Diane?
现在能确定我们想法正确的唯一途径就是下到那儿去
The only way to ensure we're right is go down there.
已经很晚了 我有点担心你
It's night. I was worried.
没事的
Nothing.
有没有想过我们是唯一幸运的
Guess we're not the only ones that struck out, huh?
-没有找到你的妻子吗 -呃 你还在这儿啊
- No luck with the wife, huh? - Oh, you're still here?
准确地说是谁邀请你到这儿来的
Who invited you here, exactly?
她在这里和我们一样
She's here just like the rest of us.
谁让你负责的啊
Who put you in charge?
疾控中心的主任
The director of the Centers for Disease control put me in charge.
你知道什么啊
You know what?
我才不稀罕 如果你不欢迎我的话
I don't need this shit. If you don't want me,
那绝对没有问题 我会走的
That's absolutely no problem. I am gone.
嗨 嗨 嗨 这不是他的决定
Hey, hey, hey. It's not his decision.
不要理他 他无权代表我们所有人说话
Alright? Just ignore him. He doesn't speak for all of us.
外面太危险了
It's too dangerous.
至少要等到天亮啊
At least just wait 'til morning.
我宁可去外面争取机会
I would rather take my chances out there
也不要和你们这些混蛋困在这里
Than be stuck in here with you assholes!
这下好了
Great.
我猜 去外面争取机会应该是不错的选择
You got a better idea out there, be my guest.
爸爸
Dad?
-嗨 儿子 -你找到妈妈了吗
- Hey, buddy. - Did you find mom?
古德温泽博士 我和诺亚正准备
Dr. Goodweather, Nora and I were just about
去我们发现的地方找一下  -稍等一下
- to go over what we discovered... - Just a minute.
你们还没有找到她吗
You... didn't find her?
没有 只是找到了她的手机
No. Look, I uh... I did find her phone.
我猜她是把手机丢了 那意味着什么
I guess she lost it. What does that mean?
扎克 我不能放弃
I'm not giving up, Zack.
或许这就是她为什么没有呼救了
Maybe this is why she hasn't called.
-1230 -我知道
- 1230. - I know it.
这个是我们家在费城的地址
It was the street address at our place in Philly
那里我还在上医学院
when I was at medical school.
我们一起买东西的地方
First place we bought together.
继续
Keep going!
Keep going.
-继续  -快点
- Keep going! - Come on!
-这就是你想要的 对吗  -妈妈 不会吧
- It's what you wanted, right? - Mom, seriously?
-在后院  -什么
- Back deck. - What?
去后院看一下
Check the back deck.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
-你喜欢它吗 -我喜欢
- Do you like it? - I love it!
-被我骗了吧  -是的
- I got you good, didn't I? - Yeah.
-生日快乐 扎克  -谢谢
- Happy birthday, Z. - Thanks so much.
你是世上最好的妈妈了 我超喜欢蓝色
You're the best mom, ever! I love the blue.
这正是我想要的
It's exactly what I wanted...
新浪微博@SSK字幕组·合作贴吧《美剧血族》吧
更多精彩内容敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
如果你对这部剧有什么看法请进入百度贴吧《美剧血族》吧